Tezza, Embali Happy!
In other words, I'm not going to chomp on you, Ueda-senpai, who can give me a hint.
Why, melon from such-and-such, melon from such-and-such
The floor is boiling at the same time the bath is boiling!
Let's go!
Rock-paper-scissors, Choky for those in the know!
A champion is born every week without fail!
Japan's richest and most rowdy prize race has begun!
Week 1
A very narrow competition specializing in rhythm stories
The Rhythm Neta Grandprix that sticks in the new era!
Who will win the heated battle and be crowned champion?
The first contestants are
Eight years after their formation, the wizards of human beat box
turned into a daily prize winner!
Watanabe Entertainment's new harmonica!
Hi, this is my new harmonica, please.
Thank you for your hard work.
As we go about our daily lives, don't you think there's a lot of background music in the house?
What do you mean?
For example, the sound when the bathtub boils, or when the rice cooker cooks rice...
There's a lot more than you think.
That melody and my freestyle upbeat verses, they're buzzing all over Japan.
Don't get carried away, man. You're getting carried away.
I've been thinking.
You've been thinking?
I want to share it with you.
Well, let's hear it then.
I'll start with the background music when the bathtub comes on.
If you hear me rapping in the bathtub... and the water is bubbling... and the water is bubbling...
Really? Really?
Play the best beat you've ever heard.
I'll do my best one verse.
Just the verse.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
I'm about to take a bath
Three, two, one, let's go
Work hard, work hard, all day long, the bathwater's soaking in.
Are you guys tired? I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired
The floor's ready, the bath's ready Let's go!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
There's no time for such a noisy bath
Shut up!
My face will be on the screen when you enter the building.
You're disgusting. You're disgusting.
No? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Next, the rice cooker.
If you hear me rapping from the rice cooker.
I'll be like, "Oh, my God, it's dinner." I won't, so it's nothing.
It's not gonna happen. It's not gonna happen.
Let's just do it. Play the best beat you've ever heard.
Yeah, okay.
I'll make the rice dance.
What's a guy like rice saying?
ugly, ugly, ugly, ugly, ugly...
I'm about to cook rice.
Three, two, one.
Ladies and gentlemen, dinner is waiting.
It's just like those rice cookers.
Rice boast and trebbian
I'm a rice, rice, rice, rice, rice Dian.
Let's go!
I wonder what's for dinner.
Looking forward to some rice?
It's showtime now
I'm no music, no rice
That's not cool.
Dumbass.
Oh, my God.
You're so dorky.
Last but not least, Princess Otohime.
Princess Otohime, we don't have a bathroom in the house.
I think you should hear me rapping through the lights.
Oh, shit.
It's dirty, it's dirty, it's dirty.
It's so dirty.
Because it's gonna be
I'm rapping.
I'm gonna make you so hungry, you're gonna get sick to your stomach.
You're gonna have to have a bowel movement.
I'm gonna have to go to the bathroom.
I'll pull down my pants
I'm pooping and flushing beets.
What's going on?
My stomach hurts.
It's embarrassing.
There's the Princess of Sound.
Let's push.
Beep.
Busu-busu-busu...
I pushed the Princess of Sound.
You're so cute, little girl.
I'm so embarrassed.
Don't worry about it.
I'm your spokesperson.
Here we go...
Come on, come on, come on.
I'm so embarrassed.
Thank you very much.
There's a battle every day that you can't lose.
The last show race of the week.
Show race every day
Produced bye bye
Come on, this show is about
We will spotlight people who are good at what they do in a very narrow genre
in a very narrow genre.
Every week, a champion of some kind will be born!
And this time, the show race is
The Rhythm Neta Grand Prix that sticks in the new age!
The show race is dedicated to the question of whether or not a piece of rhythm material will appeal to people living in the new age.
This is a show race dedicated to the question of whether or not rhythm material will appeal to people living in the new age.
The level was high from the first group.
They really kicked it up a notch, didn't they?
Did you guys enjoy the show?
It's like you're in charge here, Mr. Saito.
I see.
Yes, that's right.
For the new generation.
I'm trying to reach a new generation.
I'm a young man. I'm the enemy.
The new generation?
The TikTok generation.
Or the TikTok generation, or the social networking generation.
But to the Onba and Plus generation, we're the ones who will be stung.
I wonder what they're doing.
They're gone.
Are you sure you don't want to see her in a different outfit?
You didn't say anything.
We're only talking about Omba and Plus.
There's no way they're separate female figures.
I'm sorry.
If we change the subject...
You should take it back too.
We're talking about a different female form.
That's impossible.
No way.
Thank you very much.
This is a great place.
This place is great.
How was the site?
Well, it was great.
The rhymes, the rhythm...
It was so fast.
It just hit me.
It really stuck.
It's hard, isn't it?
I'm glad.
They were laughing so hard at the site.
I'm so happy.
I'm looking forward to seeing you in the North.
I'm looking forward to it.
Well then, Mr. Saito, please announce the scores.
Yes, sir.
Eighty points.
Oh!
Eighty.
So-so.
so-so so-so
so-so, so-so, so-so
By the way, the site's personal score and
The rest of the scores are based on the general public's point of view, so I'm not sure if I'm right or not.
Let's get some general comments.
Let's see what the reviewers have to say.
I thought it was a little low at first.
At first, I thought I'd give it a low score.
But then I thought...
I thought I should raise it a little.
80 points with a pause
80 points with a pause.
I wasn't sure about that...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, Bessler.
Bessler
Female Bessler
Female Bessler's
No, no, no, no.
And now, let's go to our second contestant.
Entry number two.
A supernova formed in 2021!
The rhythm created by the brain of a graduate of Waseda University
They will create a whirlwind of laughter.
Belonging to Grape Company
Tsun Tsun Tsun Expo
GRAPE COMPANY
grape company
Yes, I'm a pizza man.
Meri-Meri Pizza, everybody happy.
It's a pizza time.
Meri-Meri Pizza, everybody's happy.
Samba
Sambar.
Pizzana.
What is this?
Pizza
What is that?
What am I getting?
Pizza
What in my hand?
What in my pocket?
Pizza
What in my shoes?
What on my watch?
Tiny pizza
Hi, I'm Pizza Man. It's a pizza time.
Everybody happy.
It's a pizza time.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Everybody happy.
It's a pizza time.
Hey, Pizza Man.
Why did you become Pizza Man when you quit your job?
Pizza
Hey, what did Pizza do to you?
Hey, Pizza
Hey, it's me.
Pizza
It's me.
What?
Why didn't you say anything?
Pizza is the best
Hey.
You are getting a lot of money.
Pizza is the best
Also,
When did you get so many people?
Pizza is the best
Hi, I'm Pizza Man. It's a pizza time.
It seems like something good.
It's valuable.
It's a pizza time.
That much energy.
Everybody happy.
What in my hand?
In, in, in, in, in, in, in!
Oh, you're so good!
And, and, and, and, and, and, and, and!
Pitta's Best!
Pitta's best!
That's awesome, Takeda.
I'm making money doing what I want to do.
I'm gonna follow your example and quit my job.
Everyone has their own place to shine.
Takeda's words really hit home.
One day, two years later
I'm scared.
What? Really?
What's that?
It's a pizza time!
Many many pizza! Everybody happy!
Many many pizza!
Pizza dance on social networking sites
Pizza no Hasepiro
Takeda!
Oh! There's a little pizza rolling around in the back.
It's like a wind chime!
Hi! I'm a pizza man! It's pizza time!
It's for TV.
OK!
Takeda! I've been working hard since then!
Many many pizza! Everybody happy!
I thought he was waving at me.
I'm a pizza man!
Thank you very much.
Congratulations!
That's great.
You both graduated from Waseda?
That's right.
I've been working here for three years.
I was working in real estate.
Suddenly, Naito asked me out.
I'm a comedian now.
I invited him.
Wow.
Surprising.
I didn't expect this.
I thought you were gonna say something.
Almost a true story.
Now then, let's hear the scores.
Eighty-two.
Chop?
Two points.
Twenty-two.
Uh, yes.
Pizza is 8 slices, right?
And it came with two slices.
So 8 and 2 slices.
Eighty-two.
Pizza.
I can't do it at all.
The score is based on the pizza.
Okay, let's go to the tratto combo.
Now let's move on to our third contestant.
Fuьте no las.
Wow, this is
I'm the champion.
I'm the champion, and I'm the funniest guy in Japan, and I'm Osaki, and that's a great name for me.
And he's important.
And he's the most important one, that's what I meant!
Oh, no, no, no...
Let me see...
Well...
He wanted me to take a look at it.
I'm just saying... you should see it.
But I'm sure there are many more people who would like to see it.
Don't be such a pussy.
What?
Don't "eh" me.
People are talking.
Don't pout when someone's talking.
I'm your senior.
I'm a senior.
He's talking right now.
Don't pout when he's talking.
One senior.
Don't call me that.
One senior
Don't call me "Chotto"!
Chotto!
Chon!
Choo-choo!
Choo-choo, Gosta!
Choo-choo! Gosta!
Choo-choo End
Let's Go
In front of everyone watching
Choo-choo!
Senpai junpai senpai desu.
This year he'll be 32
I'm 33 this year
In other words, he's one senior to me
Don't call me "senior"!
When you were feeding a baby bottle
I was on baby food.
In other words, one senior.
Choooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!
When you can read hiragana.
I'm calling you ia.
In other words, one senior to me
Chotto sunanai
I mean, first grade, second grade, third grade...
Grade 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11...
5th grade, 6th grade, 6th grade, 11th grade, not sorry
11, 12, 12, 13, 13, 13, high school 1, high school 1, high school 2, high school 3, high school 3, graduation, not sorry.
I'm not going to get married when you get married.
I'll get divorced when you get married
In other words, Unno Senpai, I'm not going to say "See you later!
If you can punch well, I can punch better
That means I won't say "Wait a minute" to you, Unno-senpai.
When you're all hot and bothered, I'll just casually
In other words, I'm not going to say "Unno-senpai, Cho!
If you get a puppy, I'll get more
I mean, Unno-senpai, I'm not going to say "sorry!
I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean...
What I'm trying to say is, it's Unno-senpai!
Don't say "sorry"!
Don't be a pompous ass!
Don't be a dick, really.
Why don't you say something like that?
What? Where's your partner?
Ah, Chon?
Yeah.
Ah!
Ah, Chop?
It's Mr. Chopachi.
Mr. Chonpachi
It's Mr. Chompachi
It's Mr. Chonpachi.
Ah, is it Chon?
Chopachi-sensei.
Yes.
Ah, Chon?
Sanae Bigumi
Mr. Chompachi
Wow.
I'm not going to chop you.
Huh!
Oh, no!
Thank you for the wonderful Champion software!
You make these stories, don't you?
You make a story at night, and when you look back at it in the morning, you don't say, "I'm not going to do it anymore.
Why not?
I think they're afraid of it until they get it out there and it's popular.
So I'm going to be honest with you.
He just happened to give me a little nudge when we were setting up the story.
I jokingly told him I wasn't going to do it, but he laughed so hard and said, "I really want to do this.
He said, "I really want to do this.
But I didn't think it would be popular.
I was reluctant to do it for 3 months.
I had no choice but to do this one.
I couldn't believe how well it went over with the audience.
It was amazing at first.
It's not like that.
Dong-dong!
For a comedian who's been doing this for quite a long time, when you say you hit it in the middle of a routine, you mean you stopped, didn't you?
They're so close.
Now then, let's hear the score!
The score, Mr. Champions, is 77.
Low!
Why?
Let me ask you something.
Well, I don't know, maybe the pizza didn't get it.
There you go.
It's a little more realistic than I thought.
You're right.
That's really what people are saying on social media, so don't do that.
Let's go to the fourth contestant!
Once you hear them, your brain will start looping their addictive reggae music!
Sio Maria from Grape Company!
Damn!
She's so cute!
Thank you very much for your hard work!
Rideau!
Salt hook over there!
Check, check, check!
Oh!
Please take care of him!
So today
I'll be playing
Let's do a story to the music
Let's do a story!
Let's start!
Today is my girlfriend's anniversary
She and I went to elementary school together
We buried a time capsule together
About 10 years ago
Today, we went
We went to the hill behind our house to dig it out.
I dug a hole and took it out...
But when I took it out...
I don't know why...
A melon from the hole
melon, melon, melon, melon, melon, melon, melon, melon, melon, melon
melon, melon, melon, melon
Why
melon from hole
Melon Ron Ron from the hole
RilonRonRon
Dig deeper and you'll find
New melon
New melon ron ron
RilonRonRon
What's happening?
New melons
New melon
Comes out and ends
NEXT!
Today.
Traveling abroad with my girlfriend.
The destination is New York City for the first time!
Statue of Liberty, Times Square
So much to see and do!
Then she said
I use dollar bills in the U.S.
I've always wanted to
I've always wanted to.
Oh, my God.
It's cute that she's such a meek person, but...
But the money you gave me...
Not dollars.
Obviously, it was won.
Obviously, Won Won Won Won Won Won Won Won Won Won Won Won Won Won Won Won
Korean money.
Obviously Won.
Obviously Won Won Won Won.
And I was trying to buy
Arabic book
Basic book
Why in the U.S.
Arabic Books
Buy Arabic Books
END
NEXT!
She's such a wonder
She got hurt one day and was hospitalized.
Apparently, she sneezed so hard
cracked her bone.
And all at once.
Ribald book
The Ribald Book
A book. A basic book.
You said a lot.
Ribbon book
Raggedy Book
Book, basic book
What's more, you're eating
Sweet and spicy rice bowl
and more and more
Don-don in a bowl of rice
And what's more, you're eating a bowl of rice topped with
Gara ga Dragon
Gara ga dragon
Gongi gongi gongi gongi gongi
And for dessert
fancy macarons
ronrirong ronrong
Rongrongrong
And why not
Udon from the nose
more and more and more
and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more
And finally
A new melon
Finish with a new melon
OK.
Well, I guess it's time to say thank you very much.
Excellent.
Thank you very much.
And now, the first pair of finalists will be decided.
We're going to have to go over 80 to get a shot at the top.
I want to go over 80.
Let's hear it for the finalists! Let's hear it for the finalists!
79 points.
Seventy-nine.
Oh, no!
So, the first pair to advance to the finals, Tsun Tsun Tsun Expo!
Yay!
Thank you!
Congratulations!
79 points.
Yes, sir.
The reason...
This is the first time I've used a flip card.
I don't know what it means.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
You're gonna get mad in here.
I'm gonna get mad.
I don't get it.
I don't know what that means.
It's amazing how the colors develop.
Um, I was on the edge of my seat when I saw it.
I was on the edge of my seat.
Yes, I thought a melon was going to come out.
I thought a melon was going to come out.
Oh, oh, oh!
Laughter
Let's see who will be the last pair to move on to the finals.
Let's go to the last contestant.
The 24 year old performer, who has been sleeping in his bed for 24 years, has broken up and splashed out the head bottle.
Waking up today
Matsutake Entertainment History
The history of matsutake mushrooms
No, matsutake
eh
History of Matsutake Entertainment
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
24 years of performing arts experience, a sleeping picture, disbanded and jumped up a plastic bottle today
Waking up belongs to Kotake Entertainment
Ojin Ozzppon Sinamia Akira
Hello, nice to meet you.
I like gags, and I added aerobics to this gag.
I'd like to show you some aerobics today.
Start the music.
Elbows, elbows, elbows, hoof! Elbows, elbows, elbows, phew! Elbow do dance, elbow do dance, watch the knees dance.
All right! Elbow, elbow, elbow, bend stretch right elbow, all right! Elbow, elbow, elbow
For example, that you can train your arms just by bending your elbows.
All right! Elbow, elbow, elbow, there is a cute fox between knee and elbow today
All right!
Now let's move on to the feet.
Feet, feet, feet, come on!
Stop, stop, one, two,
Right foot, half line! All right!
Feet, feet, feet, I've been in a circle jerk all my life.
All right!
Legs, legs, thighs, pluck my leg hairs.
Last one, on my back!
Come on!
Let's go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
All right!
Te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te.
No crawl, sir. Watermelons don't respond at all.
All right!
That way!
Excellent. Thank you, Mr. Shinomiya.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Shinomiya, how did you like it?
Good response, good response, good response.
It's not easy to get a good response.
Now, will it be the new harmonica or Mr. Shinomiya who will advance to the finals?
Please give us your score right away.
Phew!
Wow, that's great!
That's amazing.
I'm scoring. Saito-san, please announce your score.
Ninety-nine points.
Ninety-nine.
What was the reason? It was so interesting that I wanted to see it again in the finals.
I'd like to see another one. Then 83 or something would be fine.
Well, that's the thing... I guess, but with that Matsutake Entertainment, I'm really sorry.
I didn't notice.
What a mistake!
Let's see who will win the Rhythm Neta Grand Prix!
Let's go to the finals, and the first contestant is...
This is our first contestant.
My name is Takeshi, and I'm going to be the baddest guy in town.
Rumor has it there's a black-on-black crime syndicate lurking in town.
I'm so in love with them, I went all black.
How cool... I admire you so much...
By any chance...
Excuse me.
Will you let me join your organization?
All right, follow me.
Wow!
Hey, Dad.
Two, please.
Queen up.
Who wants to slurp curry udon as fast as they can?
Excuse me!
What kind of organization am I in?
What kind of organization is this?
Excuse me!
I'm sorry to interrupt your hard work...
I'm sorry, sir.
I want out.
I want out! From the organization.
Excuse me!
You'll smell it on me!
The smell!
And, sir...
Black is not that invincible!
You can get stains on it.
You're a great performer!
Who are you?
Wait a minute!
You don't do this in a store!
This action is supposed to be a signal to let us through to the back of the store.
Isn't that what this is!
I don't think so!
Why is there something alive in the white hand?
It gets that small, you know.
The moment you become white-knuckled...
Excuse me, sir.
Idiot!
The white hand is still alive.
What are you going to do?
Don't give up!
You're just a little lucky!
You're eating!
Excuse me, sir.
Stop it!
What?
The manager!
The manager's mad at you, stop it!
You're shouting, stop it!
Is that me?
Oh, it's me!
It's definitely him!
That's not good enough for me.
What?
You should try it! Here you go.
Oh, really?
Thank you so much!
It was a big turnout.
It was a great turnout.
I wanted to be bad, so I wore black.
I didn't want to be a cunt if I was worried about oil spilling out.
I thought it was funny how he made a funny comment.
It was a little funny how he made that comment.
We all thought so.
Let's see who will be the winner!
Let's go to the second contestant of the final!
Congratulations!
My name is Baron Shuffle.
I'm Baron Shuffle, and I'm going to ask you to put one thing in this shuffle box...
I'm going to put one thing in this shuffle box and one thing in this shuffle box and shuffle shuffle shuffle.
I'm going to shuffle, shuffle, shuffle.
Let's get started.
Music, come on.
One dock, two docks, three docks, four docks.
One dock, two docks, three docks, four docks
Shuffle shuffle shuffle shuffle shuffle
Do you know how hard I learned French?
Fuh했とドーット...
Fuhset
оссс
One barked
Ai
Menimeni doxia
Chaffon
Dora datta datta datta datta dota dota dota dota dota dota dota dota dota dota dota dota dota dota dota dota 4
whenever ar some
Sasada desu ka
Mitasenihon
why doppon
свет .
re
rar
si
6 pack dock & 6 pack dock
ha ha ha ha ha
Disgusting
Bad
White blade
Good
Shuffle
Lunch Pack Doc Lunch Pack Doc
Lunch pack good
Storage technique
Shuffle Shuffle
Dock Dock Ziploc
Pre-prepared jazzman's treasures
Thank you very much!
congratulations!
Oh, my gosh.
I was setting up these props, and the comedian's side of the room said.
"You're here to win!
I could hear them saying, "You're here to win!
The results were announced!
Which one of you will be the winner?
Now, Mr. Saito, please announce the winner.
The winner of this week's Rhythm Neta Grand Prix is...
Shinomiya Shinomiya!
Congratulations!
The veterans have outdone themselves.
A little congratulation from Peetzman!
Congratulations to Shinomiya-san!
Basil shower
Fragrant
Pei
Laughter
I'm not a pettama, so good, good, good, good, good, I'm the lowest ranked in this competition
whoop!
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
Mr. Kikuchi, wait a minute!
What?
I think you were a little too harsh on the comedian today.
Yeah, yeah. Say that again.
You were a little rough on the comedians today.
Because there were no comedians from Ota Productions.
It was just pot and grape. Pot and grape?
I didn't see it at the office.
What you're looking at is the pressure.
Pressure? We don't have the power to pressure you. You joined Otani at Tsuchida's invitation, but you wish you'd chosen grape instead of pot.
No, I don't regret it, but I'm perfectly happy at Ota Productions.
Which agency do you think I should leave Ota for?
Matsuda Crystal.
Matsutake?
Are you okay? Matsutake.
Where is it? I don't know.
Where? Omotesando and Gaienmae.
Various entertainment agencies are located there, right?
Where is the Matsutake Office?
Matsue. In Matsue.
Matsue in Shimane?
Matsue Mountain.
It's a talent agency in Matsue.
Are you okay? You don't come to Tokyo with a Matsutake Entertainment Agency.
That's what's coming.
An agency in Matsue?
Think about it?
Think about it? I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you.
You have time for this? Seriously?
It's good, right? This is it.
Every day there's a race you can't lose.
Last show race of the week.
Show race every day.
If you produce, it's forever.